Fight for family.
Let Him Go is a thriller, crime, western film directed by Thomas Bezucha.
Following the loss of their son, a retired sheriff and his wife leave their Montana ranch to rescue their
young grandson from the clutches of a dangerous family living off the grid in the Dakotas.
Margaret Blackledge, played by Diane Lane.
George Blackledge, played by Kevin Costner.
Lorna Blackledge, played by Kayli Carter.
Blanche Weboy, played by Lesley Manville.
Donnie Weboy, played by Will Brittain.
Bill Weboy, played by Jeffrey Donovan.
Let Him Go is a 2020 American neo-Western thriller film starring Diane Lane and Kevin Costner, and directed,
written, and co-produced by Thomas Bezucha, based on the 2013 novel of the same name by Larry Watson.
It also stars Lesley Manville, Kayli Carter, Will Brittain, and Jeffrey Donovan.
The film follows a retired sheriff (Costner) and his wife (Lane) who try to
rescue their grandson from a dangerous family living off-the-grid.
Let Him Go was theatrically released in the United States
on November 6, 2020, by Focus Features.
The film received positive reviews and grossed over $11.6 million.
The film explores themes of based on novel or book, loss of
loved one, montana, abusive father, horse.
The tone is intense.